

Fort Lauderdale, FL 954.907.2097 albertdburks@gmail.com/in/albertdburks/albertburks.github.io/

# **About**

Passionate Product Designer with 8+ years of experience in the application of the complete design process, from concept to final delivery. I look at anything I design as an extension and reflection of myself so creating the best possible product is my ultimate goal.

# **Technical**

Figma InVision Github

Photoshop Maze Visual Studio

InDesign Marvel Code

Illustrator Miro Webflow

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Product Designer | Shift4Shop

DECEMBER 2014 - PRESENT

- Responsible for the internal styleguide and implementation of design systems for our marketing material, templates and client platform.
- · Create wireframes and prototypes which help to demonstrate UX design principles, as well as define and drive project vision.
- Work collaboratively with UX engineering and product management teams to produce high quality work informed by research and validation processes.
- Have designed 80+ of high fidelity industry-specific eCommerce themes that provide products and services online.
- Within a 2-month time frame helped complete the company's rebranding which resulted in a campaign during Super Bowl 2021 seen by an audience of over 100 million.

### Web Designer | DAS Group

JULY 2012 - AUGUST 2014

- · Worked collaboratively with agency leaders to design and build websites for a variety of different markets.
- Helped to conceptualize and executive the design deliverables for a numerous ad campaigns seen across the internet.

## Project Manager | Top of Google

MARCH 2011 - MAY 2012

- Oversaw the day to day operations of over 30 websites, acting as webmaster to keep content and search engine optimization up-to-date.
- Provided creative direction on refreshing the look and feel of business branding, as well as designing multiple landing pages for existing clients.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Ironhack Miami | Part-time UX/UI Bootcamp Projects

- Unravel Used UX methodologies such as competitive analysis, market research and desirability testing to deliver a prototype of an online magazine catering to the interests of our chosen persona, the mindfulness focused millenial.
- Ev'ry Using quantitative data and comprehensive analysis of competitor products we prototyped of an app focused on how to leverage technology to help the black community live a more positive and affirming life.
- APEX A scheduling and management app designed for a sports agency to help their clients make better use of their time and make access to necessary resources more readily available.

#### ITT Technical Institute | AA in Visual Communications